procore.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy Notice | Procore

## Privacy Notice

Effective Date: September 11, 2018

Welcome to the website of Procore Technologies, Inc. (collectively with any subsidiaries and affiliates, "Procore", "Company", "we", "us" and/or "our"). We have prepared this Privacy Notice ("Privacy Notice") to explain how we collect, use, protect and disclose your information when you use the Procore website [https://www.procore.com](https://www.procore.com/), or [https://app.procore.com](https://app.procore.com/), or any other websites on which this Privacy Notice appears ("Sites") and Procore services, including any software, mobile applications, products, devices or other services offered by Procore from time to time and other services offered through third parties integrating Procore functionality (collectively, "Services"). It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. "You" or "Client" refers to you as a user of the Sites or Services.

The use of information collected through our Service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Procore.

### QUICK LINKS

We recommend that you read this Privacy Notice in full to ensure you are fully informed. However, if you only want to access a particular section of this Privacy Notice, then you can click on the relevant link below to jump to that section.

  * [Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information (EEA Visitors Only)](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#eea)

### GENERAL

**About Procore**

Procore is a leading provider of cloud-based construction management software, headquartered in California, United States but with offices all around the world. Procore’s project management platform connects people, applications, and devices through a unified platform that helps construction firms manage risk and build quality projects, safely, on time, and within budget.

For more information, please see the "About Us" section of our Website at <https://www.procore.com/about>.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Information You Provide To Us**

We collect information that personally identifies you and other personal information about you or users whose information you provide to us when you sign up for or use the Sites or Services ("Personal Information"). This may include:

  * your name, phone number or other contact details, and the company you work for;
  * your username, password and email when you register for an account to use the Services;
  * the Profile information you provide us when you create your account profile to use any of the Services ("Profile") to help you and others be located through the Services;
  * information about other individuals when you add users through the use of our Services and the capacity in which they may use data within our application;
  * credit card or other financial account information in connection with your order to purchase the Services;
  * any information that you upload to the Sites and/or input into your account; and
  * any other information you may provide to us voluntarily through your use of our Sites and Services.

The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Sites or Services. Where this is the case, we will make this clear at the point we ask you to provide the information.

We may receive information about you from other sources, including your company or third parties who are Procore customers, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us update, expand, and analyze our records. If you give us information about others, or others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. To request removal of your personal information, contact us using the information provided in the "How to Contact Us" section below.

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. By posting a testimonial, you give your consent for Procore to use your testimonial in all media along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us using the information provided in the "How to Contact Us" section below.

### Blog

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us using the information provided in the "How to Contact Us" section below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information.

### Information We Collect Automatically

We automatically collect information regarding the actions you take on the Sites and Services. In some countries, including countries in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), this information is considered personal information under applicable data protection laws. Usage Data helps us understand trends in our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Services. We may share Usage Data about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers' needs and improve our Services.

When you use the Sites or Services, some examples of the Usage Data we may collect could include:

  * the type of Web browser you use;
  * your operating system;
  * your web request;
  * your Internet Service Provider;
  * your IP address;
  * referring/exit pages and URLs;
  * the pages you view and how you interact with links on the Services;
  * comments and other content you post via the Services;
  * the fact that you have posted comments;
  * the time and duration of your visits to the Sites or use of the Services; and
  * other such information relating to your devices, and your activity on our Sites and Services.

We may store such Usage Data itself and/or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Procore affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Sites or users of our Services, the number of visitors to each page of our Sites, etc. We use this information to help us understand how people use the Sites and Services, and to enhance the Sites and Services.

Our mobile application may collect certain additional information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, available storage space, connection type (e.g. WiFi vs. cellular) and information about the way you use the application. We may also use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location. If you do not want us to have your location information, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application.

### Single Sign-On

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

### TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We may also use Web beacons (a file placed on a website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Sites and Services, such as pre-populating your username for easier login, to allow user-specific messaging or to permit user-specific advertising. However, we have a Cookie Consent Manager in place to solicit consent and provide more information in such instances where cookies are used.

We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. At this time, Procore does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking, including "do-not-track" signals. You can remove persistent cookies and change your privacy preferences by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. However, certain features of the Sites or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, as further explained below.

We and our partners use similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data and where the application was downloaded. We link certain information we store within the analytics software to authorized users for customer usage and metrics and to aid in customer success.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * **Provision and Monitoring of the Services** : We will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to and to support your use of the Services and to monitor your use of the Services. We will also give you the opportunity to store, review and edit Personal Information and other information on the Sites.
  * **Surveys, Contests and Other Special Offers** : From time to time, we may offer our users the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests and other special offers. If you elect to participate in these services, you will need to provide certain Personal Information.
  * **Questions and Requests** : If you contact us by email or otherwise, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem.
  * **Contacting You About Other Products, Services and Events** : Procore and, if you opt-in, third parties may use your Personal Information to contact you in the future to tell you about products, services and events that may be of interest to you. You can find information on how to opt-out of contact from Procore in the "[Your Rights](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#rights)" section below.
  * **Research and Data Analysis** : In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Sites and the Services, Procore may conduct research on its customers' and users' demographics, interests and behavior based on Usage Data and other information provided to us. This data may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Procore may share this data with advertisers, researchers, business partners, publications, and other third parties. This information will not identify you or users personally.
  * **Service Improvement** : We may use your Personal Information, aggregated Personal Information and other information collected through the Sites and Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Sites, to better understand our users and to improve the Services.
  * **Order Fulfillment** : We may use your Personal Information that you provide to fulfill any orders you may place for Services offered by Procore.

### WHO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH

You may make certain of your Personal Information available to others, such as your name or username, for example when you create a profile or submit public queries. This information may be accessed by users who use the Sites or Services and may be accessed by commercial search engines such as Google, Yahoo, and Bing to the extent that such engines are permitted to access the Sites or Services.

We may disclose your Personal Information to the following categories of recipients:

  * to  **our subsidiaries**  who provide data processing services to us (for example, to support the delivery of our Services);
  * to co-sponsors of events you attend, or other businesses that we believe to be trustworthy and have privacy practices consistent with ours (" **Service Providers** "). For example, we contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, accounting, data analytics and data storage and management, and marketing and promotions, most of which are located in the United States. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by Procore;
  * in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or  **law enforcement requirements**. Procore will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other content and information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to or comply with legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Procore or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law;
  * to a  **potential buyer**  (and its agents and advisers) in connection with any proposed purchase, merger or acquisition of any part of our business, provided that we inform the buyer it must use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Notice;
  * to  **any other person with your consent**  to the disclosure.

### Advertising

We also may share information with third party ad servers, ad networks, and data exchanges ("Advertisers") so that they can tailor their advertisements to your apparent interests and deliver those advertisements to you while you are either on our Sites or using our Services. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons to conclude that you have an interest in and to display a relative advertisement instead of a random advertisement. In addition, Advertisers use technologies (such as cookies, pixels, and Web beacons) to collect information about your browsing behavior on our Sites and via our Services which they may match with information they have previously collected. Our Privacy Notice does not cover any use of information that Advertisers may collect from you or that you choose to provide to them. For information about how to opt out of receiving certain behavioral advertisements, please [visit this website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) (or this one if located in the [European Union](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Be Careful When You Share Information with Others

Please be aware that whenever you share information on a publicly available page or any other public forum on the Sites or Services, others may access that information. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

### SECURITY

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information and other information transmitted to us. For example, we control physical building access and monitor our offices with video surveillance; authorized staff utilize multi-factor authentication mechanisms to access development and engineering locations; and we have implemented security training for all new employees. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Sites or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Sites or Services, and you do so at your own risk. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us using the information provided in the "[How to Contact Us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact)" section below.

### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

### INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS

Your Personal Information may be transferred to, and processed in, countries other than the country in which you are a resident. These countries may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country (and, in some cases, may not be as protective). Specifically, our Sites and Services are hosted in the United States and our group companies and third-party service providers operate around the world.

However, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Notice. Procore participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.

### Privacy Shield

Procore participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Procore is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

Procore is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Procore complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Procore is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Procore may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge). at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

### LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION (EEA VISITORS ONLY)

If you are a visitor from the EEA, our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your Personal Information, or for more details on our legitimate interests, please contact us using the contact details provided in the "[How to Contact Us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact)" section below.

See section below entitled "[Privacy for Procore Platform Users](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#privacy)." In most cases Procore is acting on the instructions of its Clients, who determine the legal basis.

### DATA RETENTION

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or where we have an ongoing business need to do so (for example, to comply with applicable, legal, tax, or accounting requirements). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or de-identify it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

### YOUR RIGHTS

Upon request Procore will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. You can always review, correct, delete or update your Personal Information by changing the relevant settings in your Procore account or by emailing us. We will respond to your request at the latest within a month.

You can opt out of receiving certain emails by changing notification settings on the Sites or in our applications, clicking the unsubscribe link provided in an email, or by emailing us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice, please contact us using the information provided in the "[How to Contact Us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact)" section below.

### Privacy for Procore Platform Users

Procore collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

Procore acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Procore has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes on behalf of its Clients. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Procore's Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data by our Client we will respond in line with appropriate data protection laws.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Procore will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Rights of EEA Users

If you are a visitor from the EEA, you have the following data protection rights:

  * If you wish to  **access**  your Personal Information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided in the "[How to Contact Us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact)" section below. If you wish to  **correct, update or request deletion**  of your personal information, you can always do so by changing the relevant settings in your Procore account or emailing us.
  * In addition, if you are a resident of the EEA, you can  **object to processing**  of your Personal Information, ask us to  **restrict processing**  of your personal information or  **request portability** of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided in the "[How to Contact Us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact)" section below.
  * You have the right to  **opt-out of marketing communications**  we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link in the marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing (such as postal marketing or telemarketing), then please contact us using the contact details provided in the "[How to Contact Us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact)" section below.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can  **withdraw your consent**  at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the  **right to complain to a data protection authority** about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. (Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA, Switzerland and certain other countries (including the US) are available [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).)

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights promptly and at the latest within a month.

However, see above section for situations when Personal Information has been collected by a Client of Procore's that has contracted with us for use of the Services. You should contact them directly to exercise your data protection rights, and refer to their separate privacy notices.

### Third Parties/Links

Our Sites and Services may contain links or integrate with other websites and online services, or allow others to send you such links. Procore is not responsible or liable for any damage or loss related to your use of any third-party website or online service. You should always read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of a third-party website or online service before using it, whether directly or in connection with your use of the Sites or Services. Third parties may collect, but we do not authorize them to collect, personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Sites or Services.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Notice. When we do, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make; for example we may give you or our Client notice by posting the revised Privacy Notice on the Sites prior to the change becoming effective.

Those changes will go into effect on the effective date shown in the revised Privacy Notice. You can see when this Privacy Notice was last updated by checking the "Effective date" displayed at the top of this Privacy Notice.

**Please print a copy of this privacy policy for your records.**

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us using the following details:

  * Procore Technologies, Inc.  
6309 Carpinteria Avenue  
Carpinteria, CA 93013  
privacy1@procore.com

For the purposes of EU data protection legislation, the data controller of your personal information is:

  * Procore Technologies, Inc., if you are a visitor to the Sites
  * The relevant Client if you are a user of our Services

* * *

## Supplementary Privacy Notice for Australia

_If you are located in Australia, the following applies to you:_

Effective Date: October 22, 2018

This addendum (“Addendum for Australia”), together with the Privacy Notice above, explains how Procore collects, holds, uses, and discloses personal information of individuals in Australia (“Australian Data Handling”). Together, the Privacy Notice and this Addendum for Australia constitute Procore’s APP privacy policy for the purposes of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“Privacy Policy”).

To the extent of any inconsistency between this Addendum for Australia and the Privacy Notice, this Addendum for Australia will prevail.

The terms of this Addendum for Australia do not limit Procore’s rights under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).

### Collection of Information

Procore collects the kinds of Personal Information mentioned in the Privacy Notice directly from you when you use the Procore Sites and Services. If you do not provide your personal information to us, we may not be able to provide our Services to you.

We will not collect sensitive information from you without your consent, unless we are required, authorised, or permitted by law to do so. In this context, sensitive information is information or an opinion about racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious beliefs or affiliations, philosophical beliefs, membership of a professional or trade association, membership of a trade union, sexual orientation or practices, criminal record, health information about an individual, genetic information about an individual that is not otherwise health information, biometric information that is to be used for the purpose of automated biometric verification or biometric identification and/or biometric templates.

In some cases, we may collect Personal Information from you about other individuals whom you have signed up as users of our Services. By providing this information, you represent to us that you are authorised to provide the information to us and have complied with your privacy obligations in relation to the collection, use, and disclosure of the information including disclosing to the individuals that the information would be provided to us.

### Use and Disclosure of Information

Procore collects, holds, uses, and discloses Personal Information for the purposes set out in the Privacy Notice or as otherwise permitted by law.

Your Personal Information may be disclosed or transferred, and processed by, our Service Providers located outside of Australia, including those in the United States.

Personal Information that is disclosed to the public through our Service will continue to be treated as Personal Information and handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 18. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete such information from our records.

### Security

We take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information from misuse, interference, and loss, and from unauthorised access, modification, or disclosure.

### Access and Correction

You have the right to request access to, and correction of, the Personal Information we hold about you by [contacting us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact) using the contact details set out in the Privacy Notice.

### How to Contact Us / Complaints

If you believe that we have breached applicable privacy laws and wish to make a complaint about that breach, please [contact us](https://www.procore.com/fine-print/privacy#contact) using the contact details set out in the Privacy Notice. We will endeavour to respond to any complaint within a reasonable period. If you are not satisfied with our response to your complaint you may seek a review by contacting the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner using the information available at [http://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/privacy-complaints.](http://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/privacy-complaints)
